I am NOT black I mean that's what the
world calls me but it's not me I didn't
come out of my mother's womb saying hey
everybody I'm black no I was taught to
be black and you were taught to call me
that along with whatever you call
yourself is just a label see from birth
the world force feeds us these labels
and eventually we all swallow them we
digest and accept the labels never ever
doubting them but there's one problem
labels are not you and labels are not me
labels are just labels but who we truly
are is not skin deep see when I Drive my
car no one would ever confuse the car
for me well when I Drive my body why did
you confuse me for my body it's my body
get it not me let me break it down so
your bodies are just cars that we
operate and drive around the dealership
we call society decided to label mine
the black edition yours the Irish or
white edition and with no money down
zero percent APR and no test drive we
were forced to own these cars for the
rest of our lives
forgive me but I fail to see the logic
or pride in defining myself or judging
another by the cars we drive because who
we truly are is found inside listen I'm
not here to tell you how science has
concluded that genetically we're all
mixed in racing the human species
doesn't exist or how every historian
knows that race was invented in the 15th
century to divide people from each other
and it has worked perfectly no I'm not
here to lecture I just want to ask one
question
who would you be if the world never gave
you a label never gave you a box to
check would you be white black Mexican
Asian Native American middle eastern
Indian no we would be one we will be
together no longer living in the error
of calling human beings black people or
white people these labels that will
forever blind us from seeing a person
for who they are but instead seeing them
through the judgmental prejudicial
artificial filters of who we think they
are and when you let an artificial label
define yourself then my friend you have
chosen smallness over greatness and
minimize your itself confined and
divided your self from others and it is
an undeniable fact that where there is
division there will be conflict and
conflict starts Wars therefore every war
has started over labels it's always us
versus them so the answer to war the
racism that sexism and every other ism
is so simple that every politician is
misted
it's the labels we must rip them off
isn't it funny how no baby is born
racist yet every baby cries when they
hear the cries of another no matter the
gender culture or color improving the
deep dad we were meant to connect and
care for each other that is our mission
and that is not my opinion that is the
truth in the world that has sold us
fiction please listen labels only
distort our vision that which is why
half of those watching this will diss
or feel resistance and conflicted but
just remember so did the caterpillar
before it broke through its shell and
became the Magnificent butterfly
well these labels are our shells and we
must do the same thing so we can finally
spread our wings human beings were not
meant to be slapped with labels like
groceries in supermarkets DNA cannot be
regulated by the FDA we were meant to be
free and only until we remove them all
and stop living and thinking so small
will we be free to see ourselves and
each other for who we truly are
so what can we do in the face of all
this madness and chaos what is the
solution
we can love trying to control the mind
is like trying to flatten out water you
just make more waves